A Guide to the Tredegar Iron Works Records, 1801-1957
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Correspondence, Inletters, 1872-1957, Extent: 231.45 cu. ft. (656 boxes). (Box 205-860)
  - Subseries 1: General, 1872-1957, Extent: 194.95 cu. ft. (557 boxes). (Box 205-761)
    - 1923, Ta-Ti (May-November) (Box-folder 574:2)
    - 1923, To-Tu (May-November) (Box-folder 574:3)
    - 1923, Ta (November-1924 April) (Box-folder 574:4)
    - 1923, Te-To (November-1924 April) (Box-folder 574:5)
    - 1923, Tr-Ty (November-1924 April) (Box-folder 574:6)
    - 1923, U (January-May) (Box-folder 574:7)
    - 1923, U (May-November) (Box-folder 574:8)
    - 1923, U (November-1924 April) (Box-folder 575:1)
    - 1923, V (January-May) (Box-folder 575:2)
    - 1923, V (May-November) (Box-folder 575:3)
    - 1923, V (November-1924 April) (see oversize) (Box-folder 575:4)
    - 1923, Wa-We (May-1924 April) (Box-folder 575:5)
    - 1923, Wh (May-1924 April) (see oversize) (Box-folder 575:6)
    - 1923, Wi-Wr (May-1924 April) (Box-folder 576:1)
    - 1923, Y (May-1924 April) (Box-folder 576:2)
    - 1923, Z (May-1924 April) (Box-folder 576:3)
    - 1924, Ab-Al (February-September) (see oversize) (Box-folder 576:4)
    - 1924, Am (February-September) (Box-folder 576:5)
    - 1924, American Locomotive Co. (February-September) (Box-folder 576:6)
    - 1924, American Locomotive Co. (February-September) (Box-folder 576:7)
    - 1924, An-Av (February-September) (see oversize) (Box-folder 577:1)
    - 1924, Ab-Al (September-1925 August) (Box-folder 577:2)
    - 1924, Am (September-1925 August) (Box-folder 577:3)
    - 1924, Am-As (September-1925 August) (Box-folder 577:4)
    - 1924, At-Ay (September-1925 August) (Box-folder 577:5)
    - 1924, Bab-Bard (April-November) (Box-folder 577:6)
    - 1924, Bark-Bart (April-November) (Box-folder 577:7)
    - 1924, Be (April-November) (Box-folder 578:1)
    - 1924, Bi-Bl (April-November) (Box-folder 578:2)
    - 1924, Bo (April-November) (Box-folder 578:3)
    - 1924, Bra-Bry (April-November) (Box-folder 578:4)
    - 1924, Bu (April-November) (Box-folder 578:5)
    - 1924, By (April-November) (Box-folder 578:6)
    - 1924, Bac-Bard (November-1925 October) (Box-folder 578:7)
    - 1924, Bark-Baz (November-1925 October) (Box-folder 579:1)
    - 1924, Be (November-1925 October) (see oversize) (Box-folder 579:2)
    - 1924, Bi (November-1925 October) (Box-folder 579:3)
    - 1924, Bl (November-1925 October) (Box-folder 579:4)
    - 1924, Bo (November-1925 October) (see oversize) (Box-folder 579:5)
    - 1924, Bra-Bri (November-1925 October) (Box-folder 579:6)
    - 1924, Bro-By (November-1925 October) (Box-folder 579:7)
    - 1924, Cam-Cap (June-December) (see oversize) (Box-folder 579:8)
    - 1924, Car (June-December) (see oversize) (Box-folder 580:1)
    - 1924, Ce (June-December) (Box-folder 580:2)
    - 1924, Ch-Ci (June-December) (Box-folder 580:3)
    - 1924, Cl-Cu (June-December) (see oversize) (Box-folder 580:4)
    - 1924, Cam (September-1925 April) (see oversize) (Box-folder 580:5)
    - 1924, Can-Cav (September-1925 April) (Box-folder 580:6)
    - 1924, Ce-Ch (September-1925 April) (see oversize) (Box-folder 580:7)
    - 1924, Ci-Co (September-1925 April) (Box-folder 580:8)
    - 1924, Cr-Cu (September-1925 April) (see oversize) (Box-folder 580:9)
    - 1924, Dam-Dav (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 581:1)
    - 1924, Dav (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 581:2)
    - 1924, Dav-Day (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 581:3)
    - 1924, De-Di (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 581:4)
    - 1924, Do-Dy (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 581:5)
    - 1924, Ea-El (September-1926 November) (Box-folder 581:6)
    - 1924, Em (September-1926 November) (Box-folder 581:7)
    - 1924, Em (September-1926 November) (see oversize) (Box-folder 581:8)
    - 1924, En-Ex (September-1926 November) (see oversize) (Box-folder 581:9)
    - 1924, Fa (February-September) (Box-folder 582:1)
    - 1924, Fe-Fl (February-September) (Box-folder 582:2)
    - 1924, Fo (February-September) (Box-folder 582:3)
    - 1924, Fr (February-September) (see oversize) (Box-folder 582:4)
    - 1924, Fu (February-September) (Box-folder 582:5)
    - 1924, Fa (September-1925 March) (Box-folder 582:6)
    - 1924, Fe-Fo (September-1925 March) (Box-folder 582:7)
    - 1924, Fr-Fu (September-1925 March) (see oversize) (Box-folder 582:8)
    - 1924, Ga (December-1926 January) (Box-folder 583:1)
    - 1924, Ge (December-1926 January) (Box-folder 583:2)
    - 1924, Gi-Gra (December-1926 January) (Box-folder 583:3)
    - 1924, Gre-Gu (December-1926 January) (see oversize) (Box-folder 583:4)
    - 1924, Hickman (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 583:5)
    - 1924, Hickman (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 583:6)
    - 1924, Hig-Hoe (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 583:7)
    - 1924, Hol-Hou (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 584:1)
    - 1924, How-Hy (April-1925 April) (see oversize) (Box-folder 584:2)
    - 1924, I (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 584:3)
    - 1924, J (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 584:4)
    - 1924, Ka-Ki (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 584:5)
    - 1924, Ki (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 584:6)
    - 1924, Ki-Ku (April-1925 April) (Box-folder 584:7)
    - 1924, La (November-1926 January) (Box-folder 584:8)
    - 1924, Le (November-1926 January) (Box-folder 584:9)
    - 1924, Li (November-1926 January) (Box-folder 585:1)
    - 1924, Lo-Ly (November-1926 January) (see oversize) (Box-folder 585:2)
    - 1924, Mc (September-1926 January) (Box-folder 585:3)
    - 1924, Ma (September-1926 January) (Box-folder 585:4)
    - 1924, Me (September-1926 January) (Box-folder 585:5)
    - 1924, Mi (September-1926 January) (Box-folder 585:6)
    - 1924, Mob-Mon (September-1926 January) (Box-folder 586:1)
    - 1924, Moo-Mu (September-1926 January) (Box-folder 586:2)
    - 1924, Mi (December-1925 August) (see oversize) (Box-folder 586:3)
    - 1924, Mob-Mos (December-1925 August) (Box-folder 586:4)
    - 1924, Mot-My (December-1925 August) (Box-folder 586:5)
    - 1924, Na-Ne (May-November) (Box-folder 586:6)
    - 1924, Ni-No (May-November) (see oversize) (Box-folder 587:1)
    - 1924, Na-Ne (November-1925 April) (Box-folder 587:2)
    - 1924, No (November-1925 April) (Box-folder 587:3)
    - 1924, O (May-November) (Box-folder 587:4)
    - 1924, O (November-1925 April) (Box-folder 587:5)
    - 1924, Pa-Pe (May-November) (Box-folder 587:6)
    - 1924, Ph-Pr (May-November) (Box-folder 587:7)
    - 1924, Pa (November-1925 April) (Box-folder 587:8)
    - 1924, Pe-Ph (November-1925 April) (Box-folder 587:9)
    - 1924, Pi-Pu (November-1925 April) (Box-folder 588:1)
    - 1924, Q (January-September) (Box-folder 588:2)
    - 1924, Q (September-1925 April) (Box-folder 588:3)
    - 1924, Ra-Re (January-September) (Box-folder 588:4)
    - 1924, Ric (January-September) (Box-folder 588:5)
    - 1924, Ric (January-September) (Box-folder 588:6)
    - 1924, Ro-Ru (January-September) (Box-folder 588:7)
    - 1924, Ra-Re (September-1925 April) (Box-folder 588:8)
    - 1924, Ric (September-1925 April) (see oversize) (Box-folder 588:9)
    - 1924, Ric-Rit (September-1925 April) (Box-folder 589:1)
    - 1924, Ro-Ru (September-1925 April) (Box-folder 589:2)
    - 1924, Sa-Sc (March-December) (Box-folder 589:3)
    - 1924, Seaboard Airline Railway Co. (March-December) (Box-folder 589:4)
    - 1924, Sears-Sew (March-December) (Box-folder 589:5)
    - 1924, Sh-Sl (March-December) (Box-folder 589:6)
    - 1924, Sa-Sc (December-1925 August) (Box-folder 589:7)
    - 1924, Se (December-1925 August) (Box-folder 589:8)
    - 1924, Se (December-1925 August) (Box-folder 590:1)
    - 1924, Sh-Sl (December-1925 August) (Box-folder 590:2)
    - 1924, Sm-So (April-September) (Box-folder 590:3)
    - 1924, So (April-September) (Box-folder 590:4)
    - 1924, Sp-Sta (April-September) (see oversize) (Box-folder 590:5)
    - 1924, Ste-Str (April-September) (see oversize) (Box-folder 590:6)
    - 1924, Stu-Sy (April-September) (Box-folder 590:7)
    - 1924, Sm-So (September-1925 April) (Box-folder 590:8)
    - 1924, Sp-Sta (September-1925 April) (Box-folder 591:1)
    - 1924, Ste (September-1925 April) (Box-folder 591:2)
    - 1924, Sto-Sw (September-1925 April) (Box-folder 591:3)
    - 1924, Ta-Th (April-September) (Box-folder 591:4)
    - 1924, Ti-Tu (April-September) (Box-folder 591:5)
    - 1924, Ta-Th (September-1925 February) (Box-folder 591:6)
    - 1924, Ti-Tu (September-1925 February) (see oversize) (Box-folder 592:1)
    - 1924, U (April-September) (see oversize) (Box-folder 592:2)
    - 1924, U (September-1925 February) (Box-folder 592:3)
    - 1924, V (April-September) (Box-folder 592:4)
    - 1924, Va-Vi (September-1925 February) (see oversize) (Box-folder 592:5)
    - 1924, Vi (September-1925 February) (Box-folder 592:6)
    - 1924, Wa-We (April-December) (Box-folder 593:1)
    - 1924, Wh-Wi (April-December) (Box-folder 593:2)
    - 1924, Wo-Wr (April-December) (Box-folder 593:3)
    - 1924, Wa-We (December-1925 August) (Box-folder 593:4)
    - 1924, We-Wh (December-1925 August) (Box-folder 593:5)
    - 1924, Wi-Wu (December-1925 August) (Box-folder 593:6)
    - 1924, Y (April-December) (Box-folder 593:7)
    - 1924, Y (December-1925 August) (Box-folder 593:8)
    - 1924, Z (April-December) (Box-folder 593:9)
    - 1924, Z (December-1925 August) (Box-folder 594:1)
    - 1925, Ab-Al (August-1926 June) (Box-folder 594:2)
    - 1925, Am (August-1926 June) (Box-folder 594:3)
    - 1925, Am-As (August-1926 June) (Box-folder 594:4)
    - 1925, At-Au (August-1926 June) (see oversize) (Box-folder 594:5)
    - 1925, Bad-Bard (April-December) (Box-folder 594:6)
    - 1925, Bark-Bay (April-December) (Box-folder 594:7)
    - 1925, Be (April-December) (Box-folder 595:1)
    - 1925, Bi-Bl (April-December) (Box-folder 595:2)
    - 1925, Ba (December-1926 April) (Box-folder 595:3)
    - 1925, Be (December-1926 April) (Box-folder 595:4)
    - 1925, Be (December-1926 April) (Box-folder 595:5)
    - 1925, Bi-Bl (December-1926 April) (Box-folder 595:6)
    - 1925, Cai-Cap (April-August) (Box-folder 595:7)
    - 1925, Car-Cas (April-August) (Box-folder 596:1)
    - 1925, Ce-Ch (April-August) (Box-folder 596:2)
    - 1925, Ci-Co (April-August) (Box-folder 596:3)
    - 1925, Cr-Cu (April-August) (Box-folder 596:4)
    - 1925, Ca (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 596:5)
    - 1925, Ce-Ci (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 596:6)
    - 1925, Cl-Co (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 596:7)
    - 1925, Cr-Cu (Box-folder 596:8)
    - 1925, Dam-Dav (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 597:1)
    - 1925, Dav (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 597:2)
    - 1925, Dav (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 597:3)
    - 1925, De-Du (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 597:4)
    - 1925, Fa-Fi (March-September) (Box-folder 598:1)
    - 1925, Fl-Fr (March-September) (Box-folder 598:2)
    - 1925, Fr (March-September) (Box-folder 598:3)
    - 1925, Fr-Fu (March-September) (Box-folder 598:4)
    - 1925, Fa (September-1926 April) (Box-folder 598:5)
    - 1925, Fa-Fo (September-1926 April) (Box-folder 598:6)
    - 1925, Fr-Fu (September-1926 April) (Box-folder 598:7)
    - 1925, Hic (April-1926 April) (Box-folder 599:1)
    - 1925, Hig-Ho (April-1926 April) (Box-folder 599:2)
    - 1925, Hu (April-1926 April) (Box-folder 599:3)
    - 1925, Hy (April-1926 April) (Box-folder 599:4)
    - 1925, I-J (April-December) (Box-folder 599:5)
    - 1925, Ka-Ki (April-December) (Box-folder 599:6)
    - 1925, Ki-Ku (April-December) (Box-folder 599:7)
    - 1925, Mi (January-June) (Box-folder 600:1)
    - 1925, Mob-Mon (January-June) (Box-folder 600:2)
    - 1925, Moo-Mot (January-June) (Box-folder 600:3)
    - 1925, Mot-Moy (January-June) (Box-folder 600:4)
    - 1925, Na-Ne (April-August) (Box-folder 600:5)
    - 1925, No (April-August) (Box-folder 600:6)
    - 1925, Na-Ne (August-1926 April) (Box-folder 600:7)
    - 1925, No (August-1926 April) (Box-folder 601:1)
    - 1925, O (April-August) (Box-folder 601:2)
    - 1925, O (August-1926 April) (Box-folder 601:3)
    - 1925, Pa-Pe (April-August) (Box-folder 601:4)
    - 1925, Ph-Pu (April-August) (Box-folder 601:5)
    - 1925, Pa-Pe (August-1926 April) (Box-folder 601:6)
    - 1925, Ph-Pi (August-1926 April) (Box-folder 601:7)
    - 1925, Pi-Po (August-1926 April) (Box-folder 601:8)
    - 1925, Q (October-1926 April) (Box-folder 602:1)
    - 1925, Ra-Ri (April-October) (Box-folder 602:2)
    - 1925, Ri (April-October) (Box-folder 602:3)
    - 1925, Rob (April-October) (Box-folder 602:4)
    - 1925, Roc-Ru (April-October) (Box-folder 602:5)
    - 1925, Ra-Ri (October-1926 April) (Box-folder 602:6)
    - 1925, Ri (October-1926 April) (Box-folder 602:7)
    - 1925, Rob-Roc (October-1926 April) (Box-folder 602:8)
    - 1925, Rog-Ry (October-1926 April) (Box-folder 603:1)
    - 1925, Sa-Se (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 603:2)
    - 1925, Se (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 603:3)
    - 1925, Se-Sl (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 603:4)
    - 1925, Sm-Sp (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 603:5)
    - 1925, Sta (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 603:6)
    - 1925, Sta-Ste (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 603:7)
    - 1925, Sto-Sty (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 604:1)
    - 1925, Ta-Th (January-August) (Box-folder 604:2)
    - 1925, Ti (January-August) (Box-folder 604:3)
    - 1925, To-Tu (January-August) (Box-folder 604:4)
    - 1925, Ta-Th (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 604:5)
    - 1925, Ti-To (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 604:6)
    - 1925, Tr-Tu (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 604:7)
    - 1925, U (January-August) (Box-folder 604:8)
    - 1925, U (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 605:1)
    - 1925, V (January-August) (Box-folder 605:2)
    - 1925, V (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 605:3)
    - 1925, Wa-Wei (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 605:4)
    - 1925, Wel-Wes (August-1926 January) (see oversize) (Box-folder 605:5)
    - 1925, Wh-Wr (August-1926 January) (see oversize) (Box-folder 605:6)
    - 1925, Z (August-1926 January) (Box-folder 605:7)
    - 1926, Ab-Al (June-1927 June) (see oversize) (Box-folder 605:8)
    - 1926, Am (June-1927 June) (see oversize) (Box-folder 606:1)
    - 1926, An-At (June-1927 June) (Box-folder 606:2)
    - 1926, At-Au (June-1927 June) (Box-folder 606:3)
    - 1926, Bag-Bard (April-November) (Box-folder 606:4)
    - 1926, Bark-Bay (April-November) (Box-folder 606:5)
    - 1926, Be (April-November) (Box-folder 606:6)
    - 1926, Bi (April-November) (Box-folder 606:7)
    - 1926, Bl (April-1927 February) (Box-folder 607:1)
    - 1926, Bo-Bri (April-1927 February) (Box-folder 607:2)
    - 1926, Bro-Bry (April-1927 February) (Box-folder 607:3)
    - 1926, Bu-By (April-1927 February) (Box-folder 607:4)
    - 1926, Bai-Bard (November-1927 July) (see oversize) (Box-folder 607:5)
    - 1926, Bark-Bay (November-1927 July) (Box-folder 607:6)
    - 1926, Be (November-1927 July) (Box-folder 607:7)
    - 1926, Bin (November-1927 July) (Box-folder 608:1)
    - 1926, Bir-Bis (November-1927 July) (Box-folder 608:2)
    - 1926, Ca (January-June) (see oversize) (Box-folder 608:3)
    - 1926, Ce-Ch (January-June) (Box-folder 608:4)
    - 1926, Ci-Co (January-June) (Box-folder 608:5)
    - 1926, Cr-Cu (January-June) (Box-folder 608:6)
    - 1926, Cai-Cap (June-December) (see oversize) (Box-folder 608:7)
    - 1926, Car (June-December) (Box-folder 609:1)
    - 1926, Ce-Ch (June-December) (Box-folder 609:2)
    - 1926, Ci-Coo (June-December) (see oversize) (Box-folder 609:3)
    - 1926, Cor-Cu (June-December) (Box-folder 609:4)
    - 1926, Ca (December-1927 June) (Box-folder 609:5)
    - 1926, Ce-Ch (December-1927 June) (Box-folder 609:6)
    - 1926, Ci-Coo (December-1927 June) (see oversize) (Box-folder 609:7)
    - 1926, Cor-Cu (December-1927 June) (Box-folder 610:1)
    - 1926, Dam-Dav (January-November) (Box-folder 610:2)
    - 1926, Dav (January-November) (Box-folder 610:3)
    - 1926, Dav (January-November) (Box-folder 610:4)
    - 1926, De-Du (January-November) (Box-folder 610:5)
    - 1926, Dai-Dav (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 610:6)
    - 1926, Dav (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 610:7)
    - 1926, Dav (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 611:1)
    - 1926, De-Du (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 611:2)
    - 1926, Ea-El (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 611:3)
    - 1926, Em (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 611:4)
    - 1926, Em-Ev (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 611:5)
    - 1926, Fa (April-1927 March) (Box-folder 611:6)
    - 1926, Fe-Fi (April-1927 March) (Box-folder 611:7)
    - 1926, Fl-Fo (April-1927 March) (Box-folder 612:1)
    - 1926, Fr (April-1927 March) (Box-folder 612:2)
    - 1926, Fr-Fu (April-1927 March) (Box-folder 612:3)
    - 1926, Ga-Ge (January-November) (Box-folder 612:4)
    - 1926, Gi-Gra (January-November) (Box-folder 612:5)
    - 1926, Gre-Gu (January-November) (Box-folder 612:6)
    - 1926, Ga-Ge (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 612:7)
    - 1926, Gi-Gree (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 613:1)
    - 1926, Greg-Gu (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 613:2)
    - 1926, Hac-Hard (March-November) (Box-folder 613:3)
    - 1926, Harr-Hay (March-November) (Box-folder 613:4)
    - 1926, He (March-November) (Box-folder 613:5)
    - 1926, Hic-Hil (April-November) (Box-folder 614:1)
    - 1926, Hin-Hu (April-November) (Box-folder 614:2)
    - 1926, Hy (April-November) (Box-folder 614:3)
    - 1926, Hai-Hard (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 614:4)
    - 1926, Harr-Hay (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 614:5)
    - 1926, He (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 614:6)
    - 1926, Hi (November-1928 March) (Box-folder 615:1)
    - 1926, Ho (November-1928 March) (Box-folder 615:2)
    - 1926, Hu-Hy (November-1928 March) (Box-folder 615:3)
    - 1926, Hy (November-1928 March) (Box-folder 615:4)
    - 1926, I (January-1927 March) (see oversize) (Box-folder 615:5)
    - 1926, J (January-1927 March) (see oversize) (Box-folder 615:6)
    - 1926, Ka-Ki (January-1927 March) (Box-folder 615:7)
    - 1926, Ki-Ku (January-1927 March) (Box-folder 616:1)
    - 1926, La (January-June) (Box-folder 616:2)
    - 1926, Le-Li (January-June) (Box-folder 616:3)
    - 1926, Li-Lu (January-June) (Box-folder 616:4)
    - 1926, La (June-1927 March) (Box-folder 616:5)
    - 1926, Le (June-1927 March) (see oversize) (Box-folder 616:6)
    - 1926, Li (June-1927 March) (Box-folder 616:7)
    - 1926, Lo-Ly (June-1927 March) (Box-folder 617:1)
    - 1926, Mc (January-1927 June) (see oversize) (Box-folder 617:2)
    - 1926, Ma (January-1927 June) (Box-folder 617:3)
    - 1926, Me (January-1927 June) (Box-folder 617:4)
    - 1926, Mi (January-1927 June) (Box-folder 617:5)
    - 1926, Moa-Mor (January-1927 June) (Box-folder 617:6)
    - 1926, Mot (January-1927 June) (Box-folder 617:7)
    - 1926, Mot-My (January-1927 June) (Box-folder 618:1)
    - 1926, Na-Ne (April-November) (Box-folder 618:2)
    - 1926, No (April-November) (Box-folder 618:3)
    - 1926, Na-Ne (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 618:4)
    - 1926, No (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 618:5)
    - 1926, O (April-November) (Box-folder 618:6)
    - 1926, O (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 618:7)
    - 1926, Pa (April-November) (see oversize) (Box-folder 618:8)
    - 1926, Pe-Pi (April-November) (see oversize) (Box-folder 619:1)
    - 1926, Pl-Pu (April-November) (Box-folder 619:2)
    - 1926, Pa-Pi (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 619:3)
    - 1926, Pl-Pu (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 619:4)
    - 1926, Q (Box-folder 619:5)
    - 1926, Ra-Ri (April-November) (Box-folder 619:6)
    - 1926, Ri (April-November) (Box-folder 619:7)
    - 1926, Ri (April-November) (Box-folder 619:8)
    - 1926, Ro-Ru (April-November) (Box-folder 620:1)
    - 1926, Ra-Ri (November-1927 June) (see oversize) (Box-folder 620:2)
    - 1926, Ri (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 620:3)
    - 1926, Ri (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 620:4)
    - 1926, Roa-Rog (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 620:5)
    - 1926, Rol-Ru (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 620:6)
    - 1926, Sa-Sc (January-November) (Box-folder 621:1)
    - 1926, Se (January-November) (Box-folder 621:2)
    - 1926, Sh (January-November) (Box-folder 621:3)
    - 1926, Si-Sl (January-November) (see oversize) (Box-folder 621:4)
    - 1926, Sm-Sn (January-November) (Box-folder 621:5)
    - 1926, So (January-November) (Box-folder 621:6)
    - 1926, Sp-Sta (January-November) (see oversize) (Box-folder 621:7)
    - 1926, Ste-Sy (January-November) (Box-folder 622:1)
    - 1926, Sa-Sc (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 622:2)
    - 1926, Se (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 622:3)
    - 1926, Se (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 622:4)
    - 1926, Sh-Sl (November-1927 November) (see oversize) (Box-folder 622:5)
    - 1926, Sm-So (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 622:6)
    - 1926, So-Sta (November-1927 November) (see oversize) (Box-folder 623:1)
    - 1926, Ste-Str (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 623:2)
    - 1926, Su-Sy (November-1927 November) (Box-folder 623:3)
    - 1926, Ta-Te (January-June) (Box-folder 623:4)
    - 1926, Th-Tw (January-June) (Box-folder 623:5)
    - 1926, Ta-Ti (June-November) (see oversize) (Box-folder 623:6)
    - 1926, To-Tu (June-November) (Box-folder 623:7)
    - 1926, Ta-Ti (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 624:1)
    - 1926, To-Tu (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 624:2)
    - 1926, U (January-June) (Box-folder 624:3)
    - 1926, U (June-November) (Box-folder 624:4)
    - 1926, U (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 624:5)
    - 1926, V (January-June) (Box-folder 624:6)
    - 1926, V (June-November) (Box-folder 624:7)
    - 1926, V (November-1927 June) (Box-folder 625:1)
    - 1926, Wa-Wel (January-August) (Box-folder 625:2)
    - 1926, Wes-Wi (January-August) (Box-folder 625:3)
    - 1926, Wo (January-August) (Box-folder 625:4)
    - 1926, Wa-Wer (August-December) (Box-folder 625:5)
    - 1926, Wes-Wi (August-December) (Box-folder 625:6)
    - 1926, Wo-Wr (August-December) (Box-folder 626:1)
    - 1926, Y (January-August) (Box-folder 626:2)
    - 1926, Y (August-December) (Box-folder 626:3)
    - 1926, Z (January-August) (Box-folder 626:4)
    - 1926, Z (August-December) (Box-folder 626:5)
    - 1927, Ab-Al (June-1928 March (Box-folder 626:6)
    - 1927, Am (June-1928 March (Box-folder 626:7)
    - 1927, An-Au (June-1928 March (Box-folder 626:8)
    - 1927, Ba (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 626:9)
    - 1927, Be-Bi (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 627:1)
    - 1927, Ca (June-November) (Box-folder 627:2)
    - 1927, Ce-Ch (June-November) (Box-folder 627:3)
    - 1927, Ci-Cr (June-November) (Box-folder 627:4)
    - 1927, Cab-Cam (November-1928 July) (see oversize) (Box-folder 627:5)
    - 1927, Cap-Car (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 627:6)
    - 1927, Ce-Ch (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 628:1)
    - 1927, Ci-Co (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 628:2)
    - 1927, Co-Cu (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 628:3)
    - 1927, Dan-Dav (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 628:4)
    - 1927, Dav (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 628:5)
    - 1927, De-Du (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 628:6)
    - 1927, Fa (March-November) (Box-folder 628:7)
    - 1927, Fe-Fo (March-November) (Box-folder 629:1)
    - 1927, Fr-Fu (March-November) (Box-folder 629:2)
    - 1927, Fa-Fi (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 629:3)
    - 1927, Fl-Fra (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 629:4)
    - 1927, Fra-Fu (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 629:5)
    - 1927, Ga-Ge (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 629:6)
    - 1927, Ge-Gi (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 629:7)
    - 1927, Gl-Gri (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 630:1)
    - 1927, Gro-Gu (November-1928 July) (Box-folder 630:2)
    - 1927, I (March-1928 March) (Box-folder 630:3)
    - 1927, J (March-1928 March) (Box-folder 630:4)
    - 1927, Ka-Ki (March-1928 March) (Box-folder 630:5)
    - 1927, Ki-Ku (March-1928 March) (Box-folder 630:6)
    - 1927, La-Le (March-1928 March) (Box-folder 630:7)
    - 1927, Li (March-1928 March) (Box-folder 631:1)